hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and on this podcast I
help coaches mentors trainers course
creators be able to make more money with
their businesses by getting more clients
and more leads of people that are going
to be able to buy from them now I've
been in this industry for 22 years and
I've seen what works and what doesn't
and I bring that to you every single day
there's one thing more than anything
else especially when I'm working with
coaches somebody who's mentoring people
through certain things that affects
their ability to close sales and what I
call this is personally identifying with
we're going to go right into it here
personally identifying with what you do
finding your personal identity and what
you do through your
marketing what this looks like is that
when you're marketing your business that
if you are concerned about how marketing
is going to make you look now of course
I am concerned about reputation and how
something is going to look and sound a
certain people but I'm not letting what
I know is effective marketing what is
going to sell in my
business prevent me from actually
getting clients and I'm not letting what
I know works for clients prevent me from
doing what is actually effective to get
them in my business and this is one of
the biggest mistakes I think coaches do
is they have a framework they have a way
and a methodology of helping people
here's one right here life coaches
often times talk about releasing
attachments but I'll tell you this when
you're marketing a lot of the people who
you're reaching have a lot of
attachments and so you actually want to
tap into those attachments in your
marketing effectively to attract the
clients to you so that's just one
example right there you may literally
Mentor people to release those
attachments but you got to meet them
where they're at and they already have
those attachments as far as that goes
now the other one is is that like I
always look at what does the client
desire and I'm going to lead with what
the client desires the potential client
desires not what
I believe they need quote unquote okay
so for instance in some of my content
again like in this training right here
I'm giving you what you need nobody
asked for this but I'm telling you if
you want to get more sales in your
business you got to be doing this now in
that yes if I was to lead all of my
marketing with the content of this
training probably wouldn't work very
well because this is more geared around
what people need not what they want so I
need to gear all of my marketing around
what people actually want what their
desire is what they are craving the most
and so what you're looking for is
craving and desire not need and
necessity that produces result before
you hear me wrong on this I'm not saying
to not produce results for people
because you want to produce those for
your clients
this is in your sales and marketing okay
this is what I'm saying do not
self-identify who you are by what you do
in your sales and marketing because if
you're
self-identifying as well my sales and
marketing needs to produce results for
people blah blah blah blah blah you're
not going to get clients and I meet way
too many coaches that do this is that
they stress themselves out to come up
with content that is going to transform
people when in fact that content is to
be used for sales and marketing for
attracting people to them and then they
think that to attract people to them I'm
just going to give what my main
framework is to people of what they need
and get them a result and now they're
going to become a client unfortunately
it's not the way that people work we're
taught this whole give value and then
people are going to come back to you yes
you want to give value but the value
needs to be attached to what is the
desire of the prospect of the person
that you're reaching here's another
great example I had a client that I was
working with who she helps people
Pleasers with
boundaries and we did a test and I told
her what if your best offer is how to
please everybody around you without
burning yourself out now of course what
she teaches is not about how to please
everybody it's actually about letting go
of the people
pleasing and so if she's self-identified
with well I can't say how to please
everybody in my markeet if she felt that
her integrity
was at stake for saying well I can't
offer them to please everybody because
what I teach is to do the opposite of
that this client wouldn't have gotten
hundreds of leads like she was able to
get this client would wouldn't have been
able to get the kind of results that she
was able to get just working with us for
a week in her business by doing this and
so this is one of the most foundational
things that I can find that for coaches
and mentors when it comes to your
messaging when it comes to your sales
and marketing when it comes to your
sales copy when it comes to your
language when it comes to your content
creation is that if we lead with what
people need if we lead with the
framework that we deliver to people that
gets them a result if we're leading with
what actually gets people
results in our sales and marketing okay
what you're selling needs to be what
gets people results 100% but the hook
that gets people there because they
don't know what you know right now
they're not at the level you're at in
your business they're not the level of
understanding and knowledge that's why
you're the course grador you're the
coach and they're the mentee they're the
student and so you want to bait the hook
with what the student
wants and that might actually be the
very opposite of the thing the framework
that you deliver to
people and I'm going to give you an
example of this I had a client he made
over $150,000 in one month and his
biggest thing was that he always taught
was how do I let go of
control in my life how do I let go
of of needing to control everything this
is what he mentored people on this is
what he taught people on that they had
to do this but the number one question
that all of the people who came to him
initially desired was how do I get more
control how do I control everything
around me so I told him listen I
understand your framework I understand
what your teaching is I understand that
it it transforms people's
lives but we can't lead with that we
actually want to lead with the exact
opposite that they've already told us
that they want I need more control in my
life okay and so that's that's just a
huge piece of that I had a client who he
identified strongly with um the fact
that what people needed in their music
careers was to not seek out Fame but
rather to go deeper but I told him
listen what people want is to know how
to be famous he had a lot of famous
friends that he worked with and he
himself was famous as well and he
mentored people on this and we had to
create an offer
around how do I get famous how do I
become the most famous person in my
music Niche and it worked really well
because of that and so it's not a bait
and switch that we're doing we're giving
people what they desire to use it as
bait to then lead people to what they
need all of these clients that I told
you about delivered what people
needed but they LED with and they
started the conversation with the desire
that the prospect
has and so again I find this to be a
level of arrogance that allow of coaches
and mentors have I've met a lot of
people who have literally decided to not
make the kind of money that they want to
make out of arrogance for the fact that
well I just wouldn't say it that
way I just wouldn't talk that way I just
wouldn't I just wouldn't promise that
because that's not what I do type of a
thing and they've avoided actually
connecting with any clients because of
that and and unfortunately I I don't
have case studies for those people
because they by their refusal didn't get
the results that they could have gotten
had they taken the advice that I had
given them directly and up front Okay so
again if you're looking to get more
clients in your business my wealthy
coach Academy walks you through how to
do that I work with you I come alongside
you become a part of your team to help
you get results in your business I'd
love to see you in my wealthy coach
Academy
program I'd love to see you start to get
more specific more more
specific about who do you help how do
you help them what are their desires and
creating offers around the desire that
the person has to then lead them to the
thing that they need and that will
produce better results for you every
single time in your business this has
been grow your life the podcast
everybody share this with somebody don't
let this go by without sharing it with
somebody and talk to soon have a going